Castañeda mss., 1950-1991 LMC 2719
Lilly Library
- Subject Files (Box 21)
  - Topics, A-Z (Box 44)
    - Sin (Box 48)
    - Skepticism (Box 48)
    - Skepticism (Box 90)
    - Speech acts (Box 48)
    - Space (Box 48)
    - Spinoza (Box 48)
    - Statements (Box 49)
    - Subjective conditions (Box 49)
    - Subjunctive (Box 77)
    - Substance (Box 49)
    - Substance (Box 90)
    - Supergation (Box 49)
    - Superrogation (Box 90)
    - Supervenience (Box 97)
    - Syllepsis (Box 81)
    - Symbolic Logic (Box 96)
    - Synthetic a priori (Box 49)
    - Taxonomy (Box 49)
    - Taxonomy (Box 90)
    - Teleology (Box 49)
    - Tenses (Box 49)
    - Tenses (Box 100)
    - Theoretical constructs (Box 49)
    - Theories: scientific (Box 49)
    - Things (Box 49)
    - Thinking (Box 49)
    - Thinking (Box 90)
    - Thinking (Box 94)
    - Thisness (Box 94)
    - Thoughts: Sellars-Castaneda correspondence (Box 49)
    - Time (Box 49)
    - Time (Box 90)
    - Toulmin (Box 49)
    - Transcendental arguments (Box 49)
    - Translation, indeterminacy, etc. (Box 49)
    - Truth (Box 49)
    - Truth (Box 77)
    - Truth (Box 90)
    - Truth (Box 94)
    - Truth-functionality (Box 49)
    - Turnbull (Box 49)
    - Universals (Box 49)
    - Universality, moral judgem. (Box 49)
    - U.S. - Law (Box 80)
    - Utilitarianism (Box 83)
    - Utilitarianism (Box 89)
    - Utilitarianism (Box 93)
    - Utilitarianism: act (Box 49)
    - Utilitarianism - bibliography (Box 83)
    - Utilitarianism: rule (Box 49)
    - Utility (Box 94)
    - Utility Theory (Box 90)
    - Utility, theory of (Box 49)
    - Vagueness (Box 49)
    - Value judgments (Box 49)
    - Value, measurement (Box 49)
    - Value Measurement (Box 90)
    - Value, theory of (Box 90)
    - William Hart (Box 77)
    - Wittgenstein (Box 49)
- Noûs files, (21 boxes) (Box 50)
  Series includes boxes 50-71.
  - Agent, Lang. & St. of the World review (Box 74)
  - Noûs + IU (Box 88)
  - Noûs: comments about it (Box 88)
  - desc. and policies (Box 88)
  - reprints (Box 88)
  - permissions to reprint (Box 88)
  - subscriptions (Box 88)
  - advertising brochures (Box 88)
  - Advertisement (Box 88)
  - Back issues (Box 88)
- Writings (Box 72)
  - [photo - no folder] (Box 72)
  - [conf. paper HNC] (Box 72)
  - Plato's main Phaedo theory...footnotes (Box 72)
  - Conditionals (Box 72)
  - Papers on intentions (Box 72)
  - intentions comments (Box 72)
  - [loose papers] (Box 72)
  - Imperatives, norms & morality (Box 72)
  - Hypothetical imperatives (Box 72)
  - Ends & morality (Box 72)
  - Sigma operator (Box 72)
  - Axion-system for logic of obligation (Box 72)
  - Malcom-knowlegde & certainty (notes) (Box 72)
  - Quasi-indicators (first draft) (Box 72)
  - Quasi-indicators (Box 72)
  - On Von Wright "Logic of change, action & norms" (Box 72)
  - Consciousness and behavior (Box 72)
  - Omniscience & indexical reference (Box 72)
  - Hecdnett (Box 72)
  - Comments on Hacking's "Possible things" (Box 72)
  - On Hintkka and self knowledge (Box 72)
  - More on the logical from of action statements, (2 folders) (Box 72)
  - Note on S5 (Box 72)
  - Private language (George & McNeilly) (Box 72)
  - (The Encyclopedia of Philosophy) The private language problem (Box 72)
  - Private language (Oberlin) (Box 72)
  - Unpublished comments (Box 72)
  - [no label - follows unpublished comments] (Box 72)
  - Reviews (Box 72)
  - Comments on Richmond's conception of ethics (Box 72)
  - Review of Hintikka knowledge and belief, 1964 (Box 72)
  - Review of Halldin, 1958 (Box 72)
  - nonformal relations reprints, 1957 (Box 72)
  - [loose papers - between "1957..& Bob Binkley] (Box 72)
  - Bob Binkley - Sur Calculus (Box 72)
  - Human Action, t.s. & notes (Box 73)
  - Miscellaneous prints (Box 73)
  - The Doing of Thinking, drafts & edits, (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - Human Action, ch, 2 t.s. (Box 73)
  - Human Action, ch. 4 drafts & notes (Box 73)
  - "Recaséns, siches y la…Derecho y Moral" (Box 73)
  - "Philosophical Method," drafts & edits (Box 73)
  - "Philosophical Method," t.s. (Box 73)
  - "Philosophical Method," in Spanish (Box 73)
  - "Philosophical Method," prints (Box 73)
  - "Philosophical Method," edits (Box 73)
  - "Philosophical Method," re-prints (Box 73)
  - "Causes, Causity and Energy," prints & comments (Box 73)
  - "Causation," Author's proof (Box 73)
  - "Causes..." edits, proofs (Box 73)
  - "Ought, Time, and Deontic Paradoxes," drafts (Box 73)
  - "Ought, Time...," prints (Box 73)
  - "Causas, Energia..." t.s. (Spanish) (Box 73)
  - "La Base Ontologia de la Teoria...," t.s. (Box 73)
  - "Conditional Intentions" t.s. & proofs (Box 73)
  - Material related to Greek Translations (Box 73)
  - "Norms" materials (Box 74)
  - Human Action materials (Box 74)
  - Human Action notes (Talent, Jackson, Louisiana (Box 74)
  - "...Interpretation of Legal Texts" (Box 74)
  - Human Action book, (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Agent, Language... proof (Box 75)
  - Pensar y Hacer, draft (Box 75)
  - "Manual de Lógica," typescript (Box 75)
  - "La Lógica General de las Normas..." (Box 78)
  - "Un Sistema General Lógica Normativa" (Box 78)
  - Development (Abstract) (Box 81)
  - Thinking and Doing materials (Box 85)
  - miscellaneous (Box 85)
  - Table of Contents, drafts & edits (Box 85)
  - Philosophical Foundations, drafts (Box 85)
  - Thinking, Language & Experience, photocopy draft (Box 86)
  - "The Semantics of Thinking and Guise Theory" (Box 87)
  - H.N.C. miscellaneous articles (Box 87)
  - Ch. III (Logic...Prop), Ch. IV, VI (Box 93)
  - Logic, Foundations of Utilitarianism, various chapters (Box 93)
  - Imperatives, Norms, and Morality (Box 93)
  - "Consciousness and Behavior" (Box 93)
  - Miscellaneous excerpts (Box 93)
  - "Private Language" Encyclopedia (Box 93)
  - "The Logic of Modalities, Belief, and Self-Knowledge" (Box 96)
  - Knowledge & Belief, bibliography (Box 96)
  - "On the Phenomeno-Logic of the L" (Box 96)
  - Structures of Modality (Box 96)
  - "Some Reflections on Sellar's Theory..." drafts with edits (Box 99)